A very good evening friends welcome you are a
question facing crisis for mission possible
contempt welcome you to ask a
question okay and now we are here with and last
question of the day and here is the question
and this screens and you can only see
screen readers for you you are driving and
you must meter off switch on light on red
option visibility improve dip hong kong
and drive a greener the
visibility becomes the
ability to see the checkpoint
remains only twenty meters so what will you do at that
time your options are you
will popular mean you will keep going twenty
meter increase is enough to drive
or you will drive slowly by turning on the
red light or you will turn on the red
lights and stop
until it stops or
visibility improves and last
60 years and drive you will
drive while honking so that people
or anyone nearby are disturbed  Let us know that you are driving,
so now
this happens very often during the winter season when we are coming back from the office,
here every day we are
going to the office, then a lot of
heeling starts of the options also, so at that
time, what will you do at that time,
you have four options, you
can choose any one of the four and by giving the correct answer
you can get a chance to win exciting
prizes, here we have given you the
job question in front of me,
I once again asked that you are
driving and definitely gave such an
increase, so in centimeters you will proceed
620 meters in a way slowly with
lights on stop these lines on zonal rims
top celebrity improves for
contribution and drawing to you can be a
part of fast ninth part of the show and
will be a part of this cool camp in this regard
ring road safety aio increase
was in the name of the should arrive safe mission
possible, so we are trying  to wear and in the
more going to make it possible for all the
rules to be said for so you can also be a
part of this and you can also be part of
land school campaign regarding up to make
and everyday specifications very important
file driving and you are you who Russia Europe
tour very much and notifications video
driving and only you need to focus your
attention as you are on road outside you should be like more
aware and Ramu focused inside
W Arya and dropping decide road and
your crossing the road to solving this
tree near requesting you can be used
for the see females like you I miss you want to
drops definitely you should always used
processing fee use and
subscribe definitely and foot overbridge on the
crowd everyday solid important only one is
driving it is not his only
responsibility or someone is driving a truck or
driving a car it is a heavy vehicle of inch it is
absolutely only his  There is
no responsibility, it is not his fault,
sometimes mistakes are made from our side too,
we may have doubts about
pedestrians, here if you are on a bike then
because of you, it can be anyone's
fault, so this is just a hotspot
on the road because even a single mistake and one person's attention being diverted can lead to an
accident, if you lose
your focus even a little then you can become a
victim of any accident and
somewhere because of you, someone else who is
travelling on the road can suffer a lot of
harm, they can fall
asleep, so this is also the focus mother
bomb which is the tuition nowadays, so
what do we say, we put on headphones,
enjoy the price and ride point bikes and
routes, then put on this phone and the
song is playing at high volume, there is
nothing to be heard here and the person who is typing, even
if he is a victim, then it is
late 9 222 that you go towards Russia a lot
and there are many people whom
we have to cross the road  Talk about
people will put gifts and as soon as you
see the phone on Sunday and Tuesday, pay attention to the situation, they
do all this on the road and there are a lot of us
who use our phones and drive around,
we have seen that when we
cannot work properly, we
use our phones every day, so many times it happens that even
on Jagran road, if not, we stumble and fall, so
when you are on the road,
you need to be very careful on the route, do
not go out on the road, it is important to be careful, if
someone calls or someone calls or there is any
problem, you will not be able to hear you
and you can also land in great danger
and it should not happen that your
carelessness becomes the reason for someone else's death,
so we do not have to do that,
we need to be very careful every day
and if we take care of these small
things then we will be
able to make our protest more safe, so
that show here you can see the question
on my screen, it is related to the check,
you can become a part of it,
you can win a lot  Exciting
prices sir such in and this is our 10:30
we bring 5 questions every day every 2
hours one of ours goes
with you we connect with you talk about Rohit Shetty
and ask you this question
Sudhir request you please
support us in this entire business of ours top 10 android is associated with us
and help us in making our roach set the
root of something today but switch on
my screen the question is possible you are
driving cancer is darkness wearable
visibility is lot of meters
what will you do now the time when you are typing now it starts
raining very heavily
and there the video is left of almost many meters then
what will you do then
in the famous s20 meters you will
move in reverse because it is Twenty20 that is quite while
driving the bike slowly
with her lights on you will keep typing slowly turn on
your health science and
after the staff buzz the light will turn on accordingly  Reins Top
Celebrity Improves You will park your car
on the side and try to have 1000
likes to have, until you turn it on, the situation does not go away,
pimples do not come, [ __ ]
continuously Android You will keep honking
and you will keep driving towards the Gulf country
So join now and register your answer
and get a chance Vikram
Exciting Africa You guys this is not only
for the giver, the point to improve
and have in knowledge by others on this very
because we people know what our
problem is, what is right and what is wrong, do we
apply those things MB
in our day today life
or we break those rules and regulations,
we people know that we should
not be in the middle, if we are
sitting in front then back, even if someone is behind,
they should be in the front for the self
that
such no, in India it is not mandatory for those sitting
behind to sit on the seat  It
is important, but still, for your safety, the
passengers sitting behind you, the
people sitting behind you, should also take a
round. It is very important that if any
accident happens or anything happens, then if the
person sitting behind you is seated on the seat, then
you can avoid a very big accident somewhere. And Juju is a champion, it will
last for 18 days, so you have a chance to
win exciting prizes, you
can win many exciting
prizes now, only a few days are left, we go every day
from 9:00 am to 10:00 pm, you
can register your remaining dances,
every 2 hours we come, you can register
with them, so you go ahead and register yourself, so that the
results of this are run out
and the roles are a start for us at night,
absolutely speaking, you
can take a bath in it. You can check your eyes on our channel
and see your answers and
join us in this campaign and
be a part of it for your loved ones, if
not for yourself then for your loved ones  It is
very important to be aware, that is why our
12th June is celebrated right now, we have kept it here
that neither for false pride nor
for challan, you should follow the rules of road safety for
your life and the lives of your loved ones, we have to do
this for our lives and the lives of our loved ones, there is a
good alarm and attitude for all the
things that happen, if the police had a
policeman, there are new
fair of cameras on the road ahead, here if
you follow things out of fear of challan, then you are
not understanding that all these
road safety rules,
regulations have been made, they are not for our safety, nor for the
safety of others,
we do not have to do this for our safety, to show off to someone, for challan, for false pride, so
you can make our daily routine somewhere,
we tell you
that you have 2 hours as soon as possible, you have to
join us and
register your questions, as the
last question of the day in the screen
and you can see your driving and liquid  The
meter is being done now, it starts very quickly
and the soil was
less than a meter till the middle meter, so what will you do, at that
time do not proceed with the British
because what is in it is enough,
so we will do half, we will subscribe one by one till the time the
rays
fly in the form of chest and strength, you have
appointed and drive, you will keep blowing the horn
and keep driving so that people
know that you are coming, so
register yourself, give your tears as quickly as possible
and this was a very
exciting opportunity to buy a gift, this entire
question will be till 18th,
till the fabric, you can participate in it,
our questions start from the tip on Delhi Police
and in
the evening at five o'clock the last question, whoever you
are connected with me, the last question is,
so come join us and
be a part of this entire campaign and
contribute in making change in our daily life and
requesting you to please take along with you
your loved ones, your family members,
hello friends  Those whom you love,
whom you want to see safe,
you should ask them to join us. By
not joining us, their safety will be affected somewhere or the other
because our questions are
related to everyday tasks and
we always request you that
whatever answer you are giving, which you feel is
right, apply it in your life as well.
If you take care of those small things, if you
always apply those things to
your everyday in inches, then somewhere or the other we can
make our everyday better, we can make our roads
safe. Our curve of
everyday dates, somewhere or the other we can work on it.
You join us and answer this.
I have for you the last question, it is a
bursting Hansua driving and definitely, it is heavy
rain, visibility is low, so centimeters,
couple processes of riding slowly with head
light on snow with a lighter on stop,
improve continuously and this is the last
question, I request you to answer this question from you.
Kindle Join The Time Thank
You So Much For Tomorrow with Subscribe To